侯詠章 Jarvis Hou

🗲 fubon920831@gmail.com 📞 (+886)909750831 👂 Chiayi,Taiwan 🞧 Github/Jar-17

in LinkedIn/Jar-17 🛱 31/08/2003

PROFILE

I'm a devoted and intellectually curious computer science student. With 2 year of experience in Image processing, I have helped the Baseball Technology Carnival with swing and pitching analysis and broadcast the game video on Youtube with 3.6k viewers. Also, I have successfully lower the computation cost by 75% for mobile device and rise the prediction rate of barrel to nearly 90%. On top of that, I'm in the project about display device application from ministry of education in Taiwan, dealing with some features for the sports video like biomechanical tracking by opencap from Standford. Besides, I have the ability to work with others by git .Actually , I'm ready to learned more from any valuable chance

EDUCATION

Bachelor in Computer Science and Information Engineering

09/2021 - present Tainan, Taiwan

National Cheng Kung University

• Required Courses

Computer Project Design (A+)

Compiler (A+)

Algorithm (A)

• Selective Courses

The Application of AI on Chinese Medicine (A+)

Foundations of Spors Analytics: Data, Presentation, and Models in Sports (A+)

Fundamentals and Applications of Generative AI (A+)

Convolutional Neural Networks (A+)

AWARDS

Academic Award

accept academic award for 2021 Fall, 2022 Spring

Finalist

Taiwan Baseball Science Seminar

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Prospective Display of Technology and Cross-disciplinary Campus Demonstration Field Project

09/2023 - present Tainan, Taiwan

Minstry of Education

• statistical assistance with Python for the joint degree, speed, and acceleration to speed up the analysis process 3 times

Baseball Technology Team Leader

NCKU RL

08/2023 - present Tainan, Taiwan

- lower the cost of network for 4 times than original one
- maintain the performance of tracking to 86%

PROJECTS

Sport technology on baseball \mathscr{D}

06/2023 – present

Pitcher skeleton detection and batting analyze

• make a feature for the game broadcast for 3.6k viewers

Contribute-to-this-project

10/2023

• practice in git operation like fork, promote and push